Jesus Salcedo

Software Developer



I'm a software developer with great interest in **Javascript** technologies like **Angular, Vue** and **React**, graphic designer also passionate about art and video games. I love backend development with **Node**, **Python** and **SQL Databases**.

I like to constantly explore and research technology and new practices, exchange knowledge in developer communities, learn more and do what I love giving my best in every project and work team. Always open to new ideas and assume the challenges that arise with the best disposition and learn from them.

Experience

Datafis SAS (Nov 2022 - Present)

Project Leader | Full stack Developer | Typescript | Node & Python

- Cadastral observatory app development using React native for the mobile application and the Laravel framework for Backend with APIs for recognition of land and properties.
- Project management, Fullstack Development and maintenance of a government applications for the land registry manager in the Colombian Catastro.
- Frontend and backend development for the Avaluo catastral Web application using Nextjs, React, Nodejs and Postgres SQL Databases.
- UI design and fullstack development of Catasig virtual office using Angular with NestJs and Docker & Nginx for deployment.
- Frontend development and UI design for Catasig Geoserver using Vuels, Mapbox API for the map inplementation and Backend development using Python (Django), using big data librarias as pandas and Docker with Postgres Databases.

Orusxpert SAS (Jan 2022 - Oct 2022)

Full stack Developer | Typescript & Python

Software development for the generation, edition and calculation of routes, with the purpose of simplifying and improving the routing process for the location of clients and commercial representatives in each area, for the company Ab-Inbev.

Functions performed:

- Frontend implementation based on mockups provided under the Figma tool for the interfaces using Angular as the main base of the project and integrating additional tools such as Google API, Material UI and PrimeNG for the interfaces.
- Backend development through the creation of Microservices using Python (Django) and Postgresql for the connection to the database.
- Software maintenance and deployment in Google Cloud, using Docker.

Freelancer (March 2020 - Dec 2021)

Full stack Developer | Javascript, PHP & .Net Framework

Development of landing pages and ecommerces websites for small companies dedicated to the sale of confectionery and other products. Using PHP (Codeigniter) or .Net framework for the backend development wit Javascript (Bootstrap, Ajax, Datatables and jQuery) for the frontend.

Datascom SAS (Sept 2017 - Dec 2019)

Backend Developer Junior | .Net Framework

Startup dedicated to the development of solutions for medical equipment and pharmacies. Functions performed:

- Design of icons and multimedia material for risk management app with Adobe Illustrator design tools.
- UI design for SIE medical equipment management project.
- Frontend implementation for a pharmacy management project and SIE medical equipment management project, with HTML5, CSS3, Javascript (Ajax and jQuery) technologies.
- Development of backend for the pharmacy administration system. Using C# .NET with Devexpress and Postgresql for database connection.

Projects and Contributions

witty-analytics

Analytics Platform in United states

Full stack development of analytics platform for GHL using react with nextjs for the frontend, stripe for payments and strapi for backend.

liquidapp-catasig

Cadastre and property appraisal manager

Application for catastral manager and appraisal settlement developed in React and node using Next as the main framework, prisma and Postgres.

catasig

Official site of the cadastral manager in Atlantico

Development and maintenance of the official catasig website as a cadastral manager in municipalities of the department of Atlántico in Colombia.

admisalud-met-at-home Manager of medical records.

Manager of medical records, reports and patients

Monoproject based in .Net framework using Devxpress and Javascript technologies for the management of medical functions in Colombian hospitals.

Skills

Frontend Vue3 React

Vue3, React, Angular, Axios, HTML5, CSS, SASS, Material, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS and NextJs.

Backend

NodeJs, Python, C#, SQL Databases, Firebase, Mongodb Docker and AWS.

Languages English R2

English B2 Spanish Native

Others DevOps, Adobe Xd, Figma, Photoshop,

SCRUM, Git, Jira and Kanban.

Software Development

Education

Corporación Universitaria Empresarial de Salamanca **CUES** (2013 - 2016)

Graphic and multimedia production Institución Universitaria **ITSA** (2018 - 2020)